[
    {
        "question": "5 + 9",
        "optionA": "16",
        "optionB": "14",
        "optionC": "12",
        "optionD": "8",
        "answer": "14"
    },

    {
        "question": "9 / 3",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "1",
        "optionC": "2",
        "optionD": "4",
        "answer": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "66 * 2",
        "optionA": "122",
        "optionB": "132",
        "optionC": "145",
        "optionD": "172",
        "answer": "132"
    },

    {
        "question": "99 - 24",
        "optionA": "73",
        "optionB": "56",
        "optionC": "65",
        "optionD": "75",
        "answer": "75"
    },

    {
        "question": "29 - 12",
        "optionA": "17",
        "optionB": "19",
        "optionC": "14",
        "optionD": "18",
        "answer": "17"
    },

    {
        "question": "25 + 15",
        "optionA": "30",
        "optionB": "60",
        "optionC": "40",
        "optionD": "50",
        "answer": "40"
    },

    {
        "question": "75 / 5",
        "optionA": "55",
        "optionB": "35",
        "optionC": "25",
        "optionD": "15",
        "answer": "15"
    },

    {
        "question": "29 * 45",
        "optionA": "1305",
        "optionB": "1205",
        "optionC": "1225",
        "optionD": "1325",
        "answer": "1305"
    },

    {
        "question": "84 + 21",
        "optionA": "155",
        "optionB": "145",
        "optionC": "105",
        "optionD": "115",
        "answer": "105"
    },

    {
        "question": "355 / 25",
        "optionA": "17.2",
        "optionB": "14.2",
        "optionC": "15.3",
        "optionD": "17.35",
        "answer": "14.2"
    },

    {
        "question": "845 - 257",
        "optionA": "578",
        "optionB": "588",
        "optionC": "569",
        "optionD": "598",
        "answer": "588"
    },

    {
        "question": "45 + 27",
        "optionA": "72",
        "optionB": "62",
        "optionC": "42",
        "optionD": "82",
        "answer": "72"
    },

    {
        "question": "7 * 381",
        "optionA": "2667",
        "optionB": "2337",
        "optionC": "2457",
        "optionD": "2697",
        "answer": "2667"
    },

    {
        "question": "77 + 51",
        "optionA": "138",
        "optionB": "198",
        "optionC": "148",
        "optionD": "128",
        "answer": "128"
    },

    {
        "question": "44 / 4",
        "optionA": "12",
        "optionB": "11",
        "optionC": "13",
        "optionD": "15",
        "answer": "11"
    },

    {
        "question": "2 * 23",
        "optionA": "84",
        "optionB": "44",
        "optionC": "46",
        "optionD": "59",
        "answer": "46"
    },

    {
        "question": "55 + 89",
        "optionA": "144",
        "optionB": "225",
        "optionC": "96",
        "optionD": "120",
        "answer": "144"
    },

    {
        "question": "98 / 4",
        "optionA": "29.5",
        "optionB": "24.5",
        "optionC": "28",
        "optionD": "17",
        "answer": "24.5"
    },

    {
        "question": "67 * 55",
        "optionA": "3685",
        "optionB": "7784",
        "optionC": "2995",
        "optionD": "3885",
        "answer": "3685"
    },

    {
        "question": "887 + 665",
        "optionA": "1452",
        "optionB": "1456",
        "optionC": "2552",
        "optionD": "1552",
        "answer": "1552"
    }

]